Guide to the Brooklyn playbills and programs collection BCMS.0041
Brooklyn Collection
- Washington
  - The Miracle Man, August 7, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Miracle Man" with Thomas Meighan; "Be My Wife" with Max Linder; "Little Eva Ascends" with Gareth Hughes; "Sunshine Harbor"; "Watch Your Step" with Cullen Landis; "Father Tom" with Tom Wise; and more.
  - Come On Over, August 14, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Come On Over" with Colleen Moore; "Three Live Ghosts" with Anna Q. Nilsson; "Mrs. Leffingwell's Boots" with Constance Talmadge; "The Red Peacock" with Pola Negri; "Head Over Heels" with Mabel Normand; and more.
  - The World's Champion, August 21, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The World's Champion" with Wallace Reid; "Her Own Money" with Ethel Clayton; "The Mysterious Client" with Irene Castle; "One Glorious Day" with Will Rogers; "Without Fear" with Pearl White; "The Family Closet" with Alice Mann; and more.
  - John Smith, August 28, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "John Smith" with Eugene O'Brien; "The Referee" with Conway Tearle; "Vengeance Is Mine" with Irene Castle; "Sherlock Brown" with Bert Lytell; "The Angel of Crooked Street" with Alice Calhoun; "The Last Payment" with Pola Negri; and more.
  - The Man Unconquerable, September 4, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Man Unconquerable" with Jack Holt; "Trail's End" with Franklyn Farnum; "The Homespun Vamp" with May McAvoy; "A Woman's Sacrifice" with Corinne Griffith; "Gay and Devilish" with Doris May; and more.
  - The Masquerader, November 6, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Masquerader" with Guy Bates Post; "The Truthful Liar" with Wanda Hawley; "The Mohican's Daughter" with Paul Panzer; "The Married Flapper" by Marie Prevost; "Hell's Border" with William Fairbanks; and others.
  - The Trooper, November 13, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Trooper" with Gladys Walton; "Her Gilded Cage" with Gloria Swanson; "Devil Dog Dawson" with Jack Hoxie; "Slim Shoulders" with Irene Castle; "Mr. Bingle" with Maclyn Arbuckle; and more.
  - The Dust Flower, November 27, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Dust Flower" with Helene Chadwick; "The Daughter of Devil Dan" with Irma Harrison; "Her Mad Bargain" with Anita Stewart; "The Long Chance" with Henry B. Walthall; "Watch Him Step" with Richard Talmadge; and more.
  - Rich Men's Wives, December 4, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Rich Men's Wives" with House Peters; "The Little Wild Cat" with Alice Calhoun; "Girls Don't Gamble" with David Butler; "Her Night of Nights" with Marie Prevost; "My Old Kentucky Home" with Monte Blue; and more.
  - Burning Sands, December 11, 1922 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Burning Sands" with Milton Sills; "The Veiled Woman" with Marguerite Snow; "The Cowboy King" with Big Boy Williams; "Our Mutual Friend"; "The Devil's Ghost" with Lester Cuneo; Basil King's "Earthbound."
  - I Am The Law, January 1, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "I Am The Law" with Alice Lake; "The Crusader" with William Russell; "Smilin' Jim" with Franklyn Farnum; "Winning with Wits" with Barbara Bedford; "Table of Top Ranch" with Neal Hart; "Honor First" with John Gilbert; and more.
  - Forget Me Not, January 29, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Forget Me Not" with Bessie Love; "The Man Worth While" with Romaine Fielding; "Texas" with Franklyn Farnum; "Heart's Haven"; "Butterfly Range" with Neal Hart; "Bulldog Drummond" with Carlyle Blackwell; and more.
  - Woman! Wake Up!, February 5, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Woman! Wake Up!" with Florence Vidor; "Don't Doubt Your Wife" with Leah Baird; "Streets of New York" with Edward Earle; "The Woman Who Fooled Herself" with May Allison; "Chain Lighting" with Ann Little; and more.
  - The Headless Horseman, February 12, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Headless Horseman" with Will Rogers; "Mixed Faces" with William Russell; "Red Hot Romance" with John Emerson; "What's Wrong With The Women" with Barbara Castleton; "Me and My Gal"; and more.
  - Shirley of the Circus [2 copies], February 26, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Shirley of the Circus" with Shirley Mason; "Heroes of the Street" with Wesley Barry; "Alf's Button" with Leslie Henson; "Trifling Women" with Barbara LaMarr; "Life's Greatest Question" with Roy Stewart; and more.
  - Ebb Tide [2 copies], March 5, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Ebb Tide" with Lila Lee; "His Nibs" with "Chic" Sales; "The Marshall of Money Mint" with Jack Hoxie; "The Power of a Lie" with Mabel Julienne Scott; "Vengeance of Pierre" with Lester Cuneo; and more.
  - The Love Gambler, April 9, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The Love Gambler" with John Gilbert; "Broad Daylight" with Lois Wilson; "The Third Alarm" with Ralph Lewis; "The Broadway Madonna"; "If I Were Queen" with Ethel Clayton; "Gimme!" with Helene Chadwick; and more.
  - The World's A Stage, April 23, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "The World's A Stage" with Dorothy Phillips; "The Flaming Hour" with Frank Mayo; "The Double O" with Jack Hoxie; "Women Men Marry" with E. K. Lincoln; "Kindled Courage" with Hoot Gibson; and more.
  - Canyon of the Fools, April 16, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Canyon of the Fools" with Harry Carey; "The Jilt" with Ralph Graves; "The Madonna of Pompeii"; "A Woman's Woman" with Mary Alden; "Fair Lady" with Betty Blythe; "Another Man's Shoes" with Herbert Rawlinson; and more.
  - Her Accidental Husband, June 4, 1923 (Box 3)
    Showing: "Her Accidental Husband" with Miriam Cooper; "Forsaking All Others" with Colleen Moore; "Two Fisted Jefferson" with Jack Hoxie; "Mr. Billings Spends His Dime" with Walter Hiers; "Salty Saunders" with Neal Hart; and more.
- Watson's Cosey Corner
  Note: These programs are in fragile condition. Researcher use and handling may have to be supervised and will be at the librarian's discretion.
  - The Hebrew Military Ball [2 copies], August 24, 1903 (Box 3)
    Medley Overture; Owley and Randall; Miss Effie Brooklin; Charmion; The Century Comedy Four; The Saville Sisters; James H. Cullen; Carl Dammann Troupe; the One-Act Burletta, "The Hebrew Military Ball."
  - The Hebrew Military Ball, August 31, 1903 (Box 3)
    Medley Overture; Murry and Alden; Garrity Sisters; Musical Harts; Maxsmiths Duo; Charmion; Bigger and Dreher; Winchell Smith and Company in "A Friend in Need"; the One-Act Burletta, "The Hebrew Military Ball."
  - A Japanese Honeymoon, September 7, 1903 (Box 3)
    Medley Overture; Abbas Ben Omar and La Bell Marquia; Rose Carlin; The Century Comedy Four; The Original Three Westons; The Three Madcaps; Howe and Harrington; The Glinserettas; and the Cosey Corner Stock Co. in, "A Japanese Honeymoon."
  - A Japanese Honeymoon, September 14, 1903 (Box 3)
    Medley Overture; Will C. Youngs and L. May Brooks; Edward R. Adams; Bryant and Saville; Auguste Dewell; Al. Lawrence; Barber's Troupe of 10 Arabs; and the Cosey Corner Stock Co. in, "A Japanese Honeymoon."
  - Krausmeyer's Alley, September 21, 1903 (Box 3)
    Overture; Humes and Lewis; Miles and Nitram; Seymour and Dupre; Harris and Walters; Miss Lottie Gilson and Billy Hart; Parros Brothers; and the One-Act Comedy Burlesque, "Krausmeyer's Alley."
  - Krausmeyer's Alley, September 28, 1903 (Box 3)
    Overture; Barton and Lafferty; Dorothea Sisters; Martin and Quigg; Omato Troupe; Madge Fox; Ford and Dot West; and the One-Act Comedy Burlesque, "Krausmeyer's Alley."
  - Greenpoint Law, October 5, 1903 (Box 3)
    Overture; Gagnoux; Merritt and Rozella; Yalto Duo; Loney Haskell; Streator Zouaves; and the Cosey Corner Stock Company in the Burlesque, "Greenpoint Law."
  - From Broadway to Pekin, October 12, 1903 (Box 3)
    Overture; Mamie Goodrich; Bertha Wagner and Bruno Arnim; Saona; Mildred Gilmore; Lukens; Waller and McGill; Patsy Doyle; The Cosy Corner Trio; and the Cosey Corner Stock Company in an Oriental Burlesque Satire, "From Broadway to Pekin."
  - Slaperitus, Or, The Female Students, October 26, 1903 (Box 3)
    Overture; John T. Hanson and Maybel Drew; Bigger and Dreher; Phroso; Bells Stewart; Collins and Hart; Topack and West; Barrington and Martell; James H. Cullen; Cosey Corner Stock Co. in the Farcical Burlesque, "Slaperitus, Or, The Female Students."
  - The Sultan's Wives, November 9, 1903 (Box 3)
    Overture; Century Comedy Four; Chris Lane; Fisher and Clark; Wiltse and Blodgett; Orville and Frank; Charlotta Delmar; Chas. H. Duncan; and the Cosey Corner Stock Co. in the Burlesque, "The Sultan's Wives," by John Grieves.
  - Two Old Cronies, December 7, 1903 (Box 3)
    Overture; Owley and Randall; Mildred Gilmore; Shorty and Lillian Dewitt; The Famous Dinus Troupe; Engstrom Sisters; Emerson and Omega; Tom Ripley; and the Cosey Corner Stock Co. in the Farcical Burlesque, "Two Old Cronies," by W.B. Watson.
  - A Sculptor's Dream, December 28, 1903 (Box 3)
    Overture; Schaefer, Stillwell and Schaefer; King and Lee; Harris and Walters; Ida Howell; Parros Brothers; Madcaps; Carrie Nation; and the Cosey Corner Stock Co. in the Grand Burlesque, "A Sculptor's Dream," by W.B. Watson.
  - A Pleasant Evening, January 25, 1904 (Box 3)
  - The Greezer, February 15, 1904 (Box 3)
    Overture; Mackie, Wilson and Mack; Virginia Lee; Fredo and Dare; Rio Brothers; Marion and Pearl; James and Sadie Leonard; Trask and Gladden; and the Chinese Burlesque by Sol Fields, "The Greezer."
  - Krousmeyer's Alley, February 22, 1904 (Box 3)
    Characteristic March; Brown and Bartollite; Bigger and Dreher; Tanner and Gilbert; Orville and Frank; Banby and Wilson; Lizzie B. Raymond; and the Burlesque, "Krousmeyer's Alley" with W.B. Watson, Elmer Tenley et al.
  - A High Old Time, June 13, 1906 (Box 3)
    Musical Selections; Goldsmith and Hoppe; Ned Bennett; Nellie Sylvester; Frey and Fields; Overture; and Harry Montague's Musical Comedy, "A High Old Time," with Elmer Tenley, Wm. B. Watson, Edward B. Adams et al.
  - Charley's Farewell Dinner, July 4, 1904 (Box 3)
    Musical Selections; Cessy Grant; Batchelor Sisters; Ella Shields; Page and Mayo; George H. Thomas; and the Burlesque, "Charley's Farewell Dinner," a sequel to "Lifting the Lid" by Harry Montague.
  - Levi in Japan, August 15, 1904 (Box 3)
    Opening Overture; The Cosey Corner Soubrettes; Miss Ella Shields; Tony Watkins; Katie Allen Fox; Orloff Troupe; Frankie Neil; and the Oriental Extravaganza, "Levi in Japan" with W.B. Watson, Jeanette Dupre et al.
  - Hurty Wurty, September 5, [no year] (Box 3)
    Opening Overture; Russell and Tillyne; Tillie Cohen; Russell and Buckley; Murphy and Andrews; Crowley; Clara Ballerini; and Nat Field's Burlesque, "Hurty Wurty" with W. B. Watson, Nat Fields, Dave Conroy et al.
- Werba's Flatbush
  - Brothers, October 14, 1929 (Box 3)
    "John Henry Mears presents Bert Lytell in the thrilling, romantic melodrama 'Brothers' by Herbert Ashton, Jr. Staged by Arthur Hurley. With the entire original Broadway cast." Grace Menken, William Ingersoll, Clara Palmer, Matt Briggs, Frank Sylvester, et al.
- Winthrop
  - Fury, September 27-October 3, [c. 1936] (Box 3)
    Showing: "Fury" with Sylvia Sidney; "Red River Valley" with Gene Autry; "Trouble for Two" with Frank Morgan; "Southern Maid" with Bebe Daniels; "'M' the Kidnapper" with Peter Lorre; "Heores of the Range" with Ken Maynard; and more.